https://www.cyclebase.nl/cookie-policy/

Cookie Policy
This cookie statement was last updated on 27 August 2020 and applies to citizens of the European Economic Area.1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.cyclebase.nl (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of programme code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. Cookies5.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.5.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimise the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask your permission to place analytical cookies.5.3 Marketing/Tracking cookiesMarketing/Tracking cookies are cookies or any other form of local storage, used to create user profiles to display advertising or to track the user on this website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.6. Placed cookiesWooCommerce
Usage
We use WooCommerce for webshop management. Read more
Sharing data
This data is not shared with third parties.
Functional
Name
wc_cart_hash_*
Retention
session
Function
Store items in shopping cart
Polylang
Usage
We use Polylang for locale management. Read more
Sharing data
This data is not shared with third parties.
Preferences
Name
pll_language
Retention
persistent
Function
Store language settings
Complianz
Usage
We use Complianz for cookie consent management. Read more
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Complianz Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
complianz_policy_id
Retention
365 days
Function
Store accepted cookie policy ID
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Statistics (anonymous)
Name
_ga
Retention
2 years
Function
Count and track pageviews
Statistics
Name
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
Google Fonts API
Retention
none
Function
Request user IP address
Miscellaneous
Function
7. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on “Save preferences”, you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the pop-up, as described in this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.7.1 Manage your consent settings8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Data Protection Authority).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Johannes Homan
Bergschenhoek, The Netherlands
Netherlands
Website: https://www.cyclebase.nl
Email: johannes.homan@cyclebase.nl
This Cookie Policy was synchronised with cookiedatabase.org on 27 August 2020
Recent Posts
25 Years CycleBase
3 September 2020
Scroll back to top
